Emily Blake

Account Manager & Inbound Sales

Canandaigua, NY 14424 emilyblake62_w5c@indeedemail.com (585)775-5386

Experienced Sales Account Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Customer Relationship Management (CRM), Account Management, SAP ERP, Teamwork, and Microsoft Excel. Strong operations professional with a Bachelor of Science - BS focused in Business in Innovation and Entrepreneurship from Clarkson University.

#readytowork

Willing to relocate to: Atlanta, GA - Charlotte, NC - Asheville, NC Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Account Manager & Inbound Sales

OnSpot Social - Remote June 2019 to Present

- Assisted to raise sales to meet the company goal of \$25,000 monthly sales in the first 2 months.
- Changed various automatic and manual emails to increase open rates by 10%.
- Worked as the sole role of Customer Success, applying a new system to thousands of clients.
- Learned and utilized UX design in major program updates, including full backend updates.

Office Manager Intern

Potsdam Humane Society - Potsdam, NY February 2019 to May 2019

- Managed fundraising for local 4k Dog walk & craft shows increasing number of donators by 5%.
- Created a new format to collect information from volunteers.

Education

Bachelor's in Innovation and Entrepreneurship

Clarkson University - Potsdam, NY September 2017 to May 2019

Skills

- Customer Service
- Office Management
- Account Management
- Data Entry

- · Cold Calling
- CRM
- Sales
- SaaS
- InfusionSoft (1 year)
- Selling
- · Microsoft Office
- ERP Systems
- SAP CRM
- SAP ERP
- Analytics
- SAP
- Supply Chain
- Project Management
- Inside Sales
- Fundraising
- Customer Relationship Management
- B2B Sales
- E-Commerce
- Business Analysis
- Computer Networking
- User Interface (UI)
- Pricing
- User Experience (UX)

Links

https://www.linkedin.com/in/emily-blake/

Certifications and Licenses

Driver's License

Clean Driving record

Assessments

Conscientiousness — Expert

January 2019

Measures a candidate's tendency to be rule-abiding, well-organized, hard-working, confident, and think before acting.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

<u>share_to_profile/39328f8dbe97a289cba17429ee14e8ebeed53dc074545cb7</u>

Management & Leadership Skills: Impact & Influence — Highly Proficient

May 2019

Measures a candidate's ability to adapt their leadership style to accomplish goals using rational or emotional appeal.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/0311ccd4434beedfd1be878bb66c87d5eed53dc074545cb7

English Communication Skills: Typing — Highly Proficient

March 2020

Transcribing text using a standard keyboard.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/share to profile/

a0ea5f481ad111a398c70c1a6f6dbdc8eed53dc074545cb7

Customer Focus & Orientation — Expert

May 2020

Responding to customer situations with sensitivity.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/ dde180c1cca07640ac999657098c192feed53dc074545cb7

Recruiting — Highly Proficient

May 2020

Managing the candidate sourcing and selection process.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/995d5a6791e54e00d5dc5733e645bf4beed53dc074545cb7

Verbal Communication — Expert

March 2020

Speaking clearly, correctly, and concisely.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/

share to profile/8700a95b9a86b78fb38476b18a1b3993eed53dc074545cb7

Sales: Influence & Negotiation — Expert

March 2020

Persuading reluctant customers to buy products or services, and influencing and negotiating with customers to meet sales goals.

Full results: https://share.indeedassessments.com/attempts/ab50a7d4becce59fcd3192a25d7fb697eed53dc074545cb7

Indeed Assessments provides skills tests that are not indicative of a license or certification, or continued development in any professional field.